Reinhard at your service
ha how can this be I thought you were
dead
I'm sorry Reinhart after everything that
happened I needed time
Renard I must say you're looking quite
well this life must agree with you and
you are looking as lovely as ever
this is just like old times Reinhard the
old-timers must stick together teach
these kids a thing or two just like old
times
why not things may change but you never
do
hey was wondering if you'd sign
something for me it's again for a friend
of course here you go love Deva
wondering if you'd sign something for me
it's again for a friend Oh
after this match is over right now it's
time to get serious
the destruction caused by the ominous
here it reminds me of home things can be
destroyed but as long as the people are
strong they can always be rebuilt
ah you kids today with your techno music
you should enjoy the classics like
Hasselhoff I can't even take you
seriously right now
why not we need to find you some new
tombs what's wrong with the classics
I love Hasselhoff have you heard night
rocker
hina don't you think it's time you hung
a tap you're not getting any younger
never I will fight to my last breath why
not I don't approve of you dragging that
poor girl around on your adventures
Brigitte has made a choice I would have
her at my side
Reinhardt you know I had a poster of you
in my world when I was younger I
remember the poster my hair was amazing
you always did take good care of my
armor just try to keep it in one piece
for once
hi sometimes wonder if all that Armour
slows your brain down yeah and I
sometimes wonder if your height is why
you're always in such a bad mood
hi sometimes wonder if all that Armour
slows your brain down could you say that
again sometimes it's hard to hear you
all the way down there
Reinhart least number of eliminations
buys the post-mission drinks Lou it
shows these kids how it's done
Rinehart least number of eliminations
buys the post-mission drinks agreed let
the best man win
huh Winston heats up to us to keep our
comrades safe I'll be right behind you
sir
Reinhart you said you would arm-wrestle
me nervous nervous me
keep training and maybe someday you
could learn to handle a real weapon I
think I've got this old man ha ha
finally I beat ends a champion at arm
wrestling I heard it was your birthday
old man so I went easy on you
not strong enough
Reiter
I slay dragons
your mother would approve Hara would be
proud
well done my diminutive Swedish friend
también hey well avenge you